"There is a methodology named NLP (Natural Language Processing), very famous in IT. You could easily write any book and integrate certain mathematical patterns to counter the argument of mathematical miracles of Quran, especially when the human knowledge has far more superior than the people of 7th century. But, such an effort will not be good enough for these reasons.

	*The grammar should be 100% correct even with some poetry in the text.
	*The text should be claiming to be the word of God and the details should verify this claim.
	*The text should contain some predictions [of future events or knowledge], regardless of any calculation or just for sake of argument.
	*The text should contain some scientific claims regardless of true/false value because the purpose isn't writing a true book but a book like Quran.
	*The text should contain instructions about socio-economical and judicial system, again, it doesn't matter if they are moral/immoral for someone or all.
	*The text should contain some history or historical events regardless of true/false details.

If someone or a team of computer scientists/mathematician could write such a book, then it can be honored as a honest effort to counter the argument 'The Quran contains miracles'. Why it would be honored because whoever will try to do this, will know that it's way more difficult (or may be impossible) to create a text like Quran regardless of how much effort and processing power s/he/they put. After such an effort, people will end up saying nothing but 'The Quran contains miracles' and this kind of text cannot be produced. Last thing to say is that there wasn't any google in 7th century, so how somebody managed to arrange a text like Quran? No one but God.﻿"
	-I forgot to get citation when I copied this

"Simple to understand, impossible to imitate."
	-All over the internet


Remarks:
	-There are lots of websites out there that claim to have supported or debunked mathematical "miracles" in the Quran. Both sides generally argue their point by finding anything, no matter how small, to support their side and invalidating the other, and so things that are insignificant can be interpreted to be significant. There are even certain cases of conflicting evidence, as both sometime decide to fabricate and/or omit relevant information. In the 1974, an Eygptian living in the United States named Rashad Khalifa published research on the number 19, with the purpose of exposing the Quran's supposed accuracy with this number. It was originally recieved favorably, but then he claimed Prophethood based on his research (an act considered a lie or heresy by Islamic scripture, as it explicitly states that Muhammad is the last prophet and that the Quran is our ultimate guide for all people in all time) and people accused him of faking most of it, and as such people started having negative attitudes to the supposed numerical miracles of the Quran. However, this paper will not address the validity of Khalifa's work, rather the organization of this paper will be focused on providing the facts first and how the fact was discovered (as to provide evidence outside the scope of interpretation), and potential significances based on the fact and the meaning behind it. As such, this paper's purpose is to either support or debunk the Quranic numerical "miracles" that have been circulating around the internet, simply based on finding exact results and doing the right research without omitting any information. If the Quran is indeed the word of God, it will support itself against the false claims made by people without understanding, whether they are for or against the Quran.
	
	-Spelling in the Quran does not differ much between different books, however there is a slight variation between how current Arabic is spelled and the "uthmani" spelling (like the splitting of a compound word into two words), which is the original spelling of the Quran written by Uthman-bin-Affan, one of prophet Muhammad's diciples, and the people at the time. While this has very little significance to the word counts mentioned here, as none of the following word counts contains any of the differences in spelling mentioned above, this needs to made explicit just in case there is an issue later. For all word counts used, we use the original spelling, which is confirmed by the 1400 year old Quranic texts archeologists have found.
	
	-Any "..." indicates that I have either not finished research in that topic or have not found anything significant about it yet.
	
	-Any number with an asterisk (*) indicates that it is divisible by 19, which is supposedly a sign from God for those who disbelieve (see Quran 74:30).
	
	-Any number with two asterisks (**) indicates that it is a prime number, which is supposedly one of the miracles of the Quran.
	
	-Any number with three asterisk (***) indicates that it relates to the theory that there are two false verses injected to the 9th chapter of the Quran.
